pso-world.com 2011-06-04

# Privacy Policy - PSO-World.com

|  **Site Navigation**  
---  
  
  * PSOW Home
  * Message Boards
  * Submit News
  * News Archive
  * Recommend & Link
  * Website Staff

**Search PSOW**  
---  
  
**Phantasy Star Zero**  
---  
**Databases**

  * Item Database
  * Drop Charts
  * Enemy List
  * Weapons Gallery

**Guides**

  * Cake Shop
  * Character Types
  * Character Planning
  * Elemental Attributes
  * Mag Feeding
  * Mag Evolution Chart
  * Mag Natures
  * Photon Arts
  * Set Bonuses
  * Sewer Shop
  * Side Mission Rewards
  * Technique Stats
  * Titles

**Media**

  * Merchandise
 
  * Screenshots
 
  * Wallpaper

**Phantasy Star Universe**  
---  
**Items**

**Guides**

  * Characters
  * Gameplay
  * General Information
  * Overview
  * Partner Machinery
  * Photon Fortune
  * Walkthroughs

**Stat Calculator**

  * Base Stats
  * Job Percentages
  * Stat Submission

**Downloads**

  * Images
  * Trailers

**Interviews**

  * Takao Miyoshi
  * Kelli Sae

**PSO: Episode 1,2, & 4**  
---  
**Items**

  * Item Database
  * Item Comparison
  * Drop Charts
  * Search Findings

**Guides**

  * Battle Mode
  * Beastiary
  * Blue Burst Overview
  * Challenge Mode
  * Characters
  * Enemy Parts
  * Item Combinations
  * Mags
  * Maps
  * Plus Overview
  * Photon Drops
  * **Quests**
  * Scripts
  * Techniques
  * Videos

**Calculators**

  * Damage Calculator
  * Section ID Calculator
  * Stat Calculator
  * Tech Dmg Calculator

**Episode 3**  
---  
**Cards**

  * Card Database
  * Card Comparison

**Guides**

  * Battle
  * Cards
  * Characters
  * Decks
  * Overview
  * Quests
  * Scripts

**Calculators**

  * Rank Calculator
  * Section ID Calculator

**Site**  
---  
**Forum**

  * Forum Index
  * Forum Rules

**Fan Works**

  * Fan Art Gallery
  * Fan Media Theater
  * Fan Fiction

**Features**

  * Contests Archive
  * Download Center
  * Image Gallery
  * Member Spotlight
  * Quizzes
  * Voting Booth

  |  | 

## PSO-World.com Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

### How do we protect your information?

User information is stored on a secure server. This information will only be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their User Control Panel (UserCP) and going to the ‘Edit Your Details’ page.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.pso-world.com
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.pso-world.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
-Google Adsense

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.pso-world.com/forums/faq.php?faq=vb3_board_faq#faq_forumrules](http://www.pso-world.com/forums/faq.php?faq=vb3_board_faq#faq_forumrules&s=7331ba0208bb49570ad99dd73f20df1e)

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

http://www.pso-world.com  
  
---  
  
  * 

  |  |  **Advertisement**  
---
